export const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What Does It Cost To Use Simply Logistics Services?",
    answer:
      "There is no license fee or monthly subscriptions for signing up or access.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What Can I Ship?",
    answer:
      "We support all palletised and bulk tank transport. Please contact us for any specific requirements.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What Warranties Do I Have For My Shipments?",
    answer:
      "Simply Logistics Services operates under country-specific freight forward industry terms. We regularly review our transport providers and only work with professional and experienced carriers.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "How Does Simply Logistics Services Verify Carriers?",
    answer:
      "We take pride in ensuring the quality of our Carriers. All Carriers are pre-screened and verified before they start carrying your freight. We regularly monitor compliance documentation and review Carrier performance.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Who Can Use Simply Logistics Services?",
    answer:
      "Simply Logistics Services is a B2B platform allowing businesses of any form with readily available shipments to be linked to equipped carrier service companies.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What Locations Does Simply Logistics Services Ship To?",
    answer:
      "Simply Logisitcs Services can handle shipments via road freight throughout all of USA.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "How does Simply Logistics Services choose carriers?",
    answer:
      "Simply Logistics Services works with the most reputable contract carriers across the nation, each of which is required to go through numerous steps in order to meet the U.S. Department of Transportation’s strict Compliance, Safety and Accountability (CSA) requirements.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "How do I determine freight class?",
    answer:
      "There are 18 freight classes. They are determined by weight, dimensions, density, storage capability, ease of handling, value and liability from instances like theft, damage, breakability and spoilage.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "What’s the difference between less than truckload and full truckload?",
    answer:
      "Less than truckload (LTL) shipping allows multiple shippers to share space on the same truck while full truckload shipments typically travel on only one truck with one destination.",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "How should I package my items?",
    answer:
      "When shipping goods, it’s always important to minimize movement. Pack crates or boxes as full as possible, with heavier items on the bottom. If the crate is not filled, use packing material to plug the empty spaces.",
  },
];
